Request an Appointment

* Patient Resources
    
* Locations

Request an Appointment

Privacy Policy
==============

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which we collect, use, maintain, and disclose information collected from users (each, a “User”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Zeam Medical and Aesthetics.

##### Privacy Statement

We are committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to our Practice’s Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using this website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

##### Collection of your Personal Information

This Practice collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. This Practice also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by this website. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of this Web site.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others.

This Practice encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from the website so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. This Practice is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on any other Web sites.

##### Use of your Personal Information

This Practice collects and uses your personal information to operate the Web site and deliver the services you have requested. This Practice also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from this Practice and its affiliates. This Practice may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.

This Practice does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. This Practice may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

This Practice does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

This Practice will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law.

##### Use of Cookies

The Web site uses “cookies” to help this Practice personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

Security of your Personal Information
-------------------------------------

This Practice secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. This Practice secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement
-------------------------

This Practice will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how this Practice is protecting your information.

Contact Information
-------------------

Please contact us by phone at [916-461-8639](tel:9164618639) or by mail at 508 Gibson Dr, Suite 150-160, Roseville, CA 95678.

###### For more information or to schedule an appointment, feel free to contact us directly.

###### Connect With Zeam Health & Wellness on Social

Discover our holistic approach to wellness. Visit us, follow our journey, or reach out for expert care

### [Sacramento](https://www.zeamhealth.com/locations/sacramento/)

* Psychiatry & Therapy Services
* [1451 River Park Dr. Ste 100  
    Sacramento, CA 95815](https://maps.app.goo.gl/xSByp2kEAxmB74d89)

### [Folsom](https://www.zeamhealth.com/locations/folsom/)

* Psychiatry, Therapy & Primary Care
* [193 Blue Ravine Rd, Ste 170A  
    Folsom, CA 95630](https://maps.app.goo.gl/ta8Uw7torGRjFDB88)

### [Roseville](https://www.zeamhealth.com/locations/roseville/)

* Psychiatry, Therapy, Primary Care & Aesthetics
* [508 Gibson Dr. Ste 150-160  
    Roseville, CA 95678](https://maps.app.goo.gl/gYjGRpH4hmZFxEFt8)

### Other Links

Appointment Request Form
------------------------

Are you a new or returning patient?  
NewReturning

First Name  

Last Name  

Email  

Phone  

Date of Birth  

Are you the patient?  
YesNo

Sex  
MaleFemaleOther

Reason (optional)  

**Note:** We are not currently accepting Medical Insurance at this time.

Insurance carrier and plan name  

Insurance member id #  

Insurance group id #  

Additional notes for the office:  

1  
I have read and agreed to the [Privacy Policy](https://www.zeamhealth.com/privacy-policy-2/) and [Terms of Use](https://www.zeamhealth.com/our-terms/) and I am at least 13 and have the authority to make this appointment.  

I agree to receive text messages from this practice and understand that message frequency and data rates may apply.

* * *

PLEASE NOTE: This is an appointment request only. The office will reach out to you to confirm the appointment date and time. If this is an emergency, please call the office.

* * *

Appointment Request
-------------------

Are you a new or returning patient?  
NewReturning

First Name  

Last Name  

Email  

Phone  

Date of Birth  

Are you the patient?  
YesNo

Sex  
MaleFemaleOther

Reason (optional)  

**Note:** We are not currently accepting Medical Insurance at this time.

Insurance carrier and plan name  

Insurance member id #  

Insurance group id #  

Additional notes for the office:  

1  
I have read and agreed to the [Privacy Policy](https://www.zeamhealth.com/privacy-policy-2/) and [Terms of Use](https://www.zeamhealth.com/our-terms/) and I am at least 13 and have the authority to make this appointment.  

I agree to receive text messages from this practice and understand that message frequency and data rates may apply.

* * *

PLEASE NOTE: This is an appointment request only. The office will reach out to you to confirm the appointment date and time. If this is an emergency, please call the office.

* * *
